 const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'The capital of Albania is:',
        answer_a:
            'Vienna',
        answer_b: 'Tirana',
        answer_c:
            "Skopje",
        correct_answer: 'b',
       
    },
   
    {

        id: 2,
        question: 'The capital of Belarus is:',
        answer_a: 'Podgorica',
        answer_b: 'Moscow',
        answer_c: 'Minsk',
        correct_answer: 'c',
       
    },

    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'The capital of Romania is:',
        answer_a: 'Copenhagen',
        answer_b: 'Belgrade',
        answer_c: 'Bucharest',
        correct_answer: 'c',
       
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'The capital of Kazakhstan is:',
        answer_a: 'Nur-Sultan',
        answer_b: 'Reykjavik',
        answer_c: 'Helsinki',
        correct_answer: 'a',
        
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'The capital of Hungary is:',
        answer_a: 'Lisbon',
        answer_b: 'Warsaw',
        answer_c: 'Budapest',
        correct_answer: 'c',
        
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'The capital of Cyprus is:',
        answer_a: 'Pristina',
        answer_b: 'Nicosia',
        answer_c: 'Vaduz',
        correct_answer: 'b',
        
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'The capital of Latvia is:',
        answer_a: 'Riga',
        answer_b: 'Amsterdam',
        answer_c: 'Skopje',
        correct_answer: 'a',
       
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'The capital of Sweden is:',
        answer_a: 'Madrid',
        answer_b: 'Stockholm',
        answer_c: 'Bern',
        correct_answer: 'b',
    },

    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'The capital of Ukraine is:',
        answer_a: 'Prague',
        answer_b: 'Kyiv',
        answer_c: 'Sarajevo',
        correct_answer: 'b',
       
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'The capital of Croatia is:',
        answer_a: 'Brussels',
        answer_b: 'Zagreb',
        answer_c: 'Bucharest',
        correct_answer: 'b',
        
    },
  ];

  export default questions;